ouadmissions.com 2014-06-29

# OUCET Online Application Processing System

We value the trust you place in us. That's why we insist upon the highest standards for secure transactions and applicant information privacy. Please read the following statement to learn about our information gathering and dissemination practices. 

Note: Our privacy policy is subject to change at any time without notice. To make sure you are aware of any changes, **please review this policy periodically.**

**1\. PAYMENT SECURITY**

Our site has stringent security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. Whenever you change or access your account information, we offer the use of a secure server. Once your information is in our possession we adhere to strict security guidelines, protecting it against unauthorized access.

**OUCET 2014** website ensures that every transaction that takes between you and our OUCET website through online is in a safe and secure environment. This can be achieved, as OUCET 2014 website is protected by Secured Socket Layer (SSL) technology.

**2\. COLLECTION OF PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION**

We collect personally identifiable information (Email Id., Name, Contact number, etc.) from you when you apply for the OUCET 2014 examination. Any one can browse some sections of our site without being an applicant for OUCET 2014. Certain activities (such as applying for the OUCET 2014 Examination, Application Status, Complaint Status, etc) do require Registration. We do use your contact information to send you information.

**3\. USE OF DEMOGRAPHIC AND PROFILE DATA**

We use Personal Information for smooth conduct of OUCET. We use your personal information to check your eligibility to appear for the OUCET 2014 examination as per G.O.’s issued by AP state government from time to time. We use your personal information to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, help promote a safe service, collect fees owed, detect and protect us against error, fraud and other criminal activity, enforce our terms and conditions, and as otherwise described to you at the time of collection.

In our efforts to continually improve our product and service offerings, we collect and analyze demographic and profile data about our users' activity on our website. We identify and use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our website. Your IP address is also used to help identify you and to gather broad demographic information.

**4\. COOKIES**

A "cookie" is a small piece of information stored by a Web server on a Web browser so it can be later read back from that browser. Cookies are useful for enabling the browser to remember information specific to a given user. OUCET 2014 places both permanent and temporary cookies in your computer's hard drive. OUCET 2014 cookies do not contain any of your Personally Identifiable Information.

**5\. SHARING OF PERSONAL INFORMATION**

We may share personal information with our other education department and other related department entities and affiliates to help detect and prevent identity theft, fraud and other potentially illegal acts, correlate related or multiple accounts to prevent abuse of our services.

We may disclose personal information, if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to respond to court orders, or other legal process. We may disclose personal information to law enforcement offices, third party rights owners, or others in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to enforce our Terms or Privacy Policy, respond to claims that an advertisement, posting or other content violates the rights of a third party or protect the rights, property or personal safety of our users or the general public 

**6\. PROHIBITION AGAINST UNLAWFUL USE**

As a condition for the use of the OUCET Website, the User warrants that they will not use the Website for any purpose that is unlawful or illegal under any law for the time being in force within or outside India or prohibited by this Agreement. In addition, the OUCET Website shall not be used in any manner, which could damage, disable, overburden or impair it or interfere with any other party's use of the Website. The User shall refrain from obtaining or attempting to obtain any materials or information through any means not intentionally made available or provided for or through the Website..

**7\. LINKS TO OTHER SITES**

Our site links to other websites that may collect Personally Identifiable Information about you. OUCET 2014 COMMITTEE is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of those linked websites.

**8\. USE OF COMMUNICATION SERVICES**

centers, and/or other message (hereinafter collectively referred to as "Communication Services"). The User agrees and undertakes to use the Communication Services only to post, send and receive messages and material that are proper and related to the OUCET. By way of example, and not as a limitation, the User agrees and undertakes that when using a Communication Service, the User will not: 

defame, abuse, harass, stalk, threaten or otherwise violate the legal rights of others   
  
---  
  
upload files that contain software or other material protected by intellectual property laws unless the User owns or controls the rights thereto or have received all necessary consents   
  
upload or distribute files that contain viruses, corrupted files, or any other similar software or programs that may damage the operation of the OUCET Website or another's computer,  
  
conduct or forward surveys, contests, pyramid schemes or chain letters;  
  
download any file posted by another user of a Communication Service that the User know, or reasonably should know, cannot be legally distributed in such manner;  
  
falsify or delete any author attributions, legal or other proper notices or proprietary designations or labels of the origin or source of software or other material contained in a file that is uploaded;  
  
violate any code of conduct or other guidelines, which may be applicable for or to any particular Communication Service;  
  
violate any applicable laws or regulations for the time being in force in or outside India; and  
  
violate any of the terms and conditions of this Agreement or any other terms and conditions for the use of the Website contained elsewhere herein  
  
**OUCET** reserves the right at all times to disclose any information as is necessary to satisfy or comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request, or to edit, refuse to post or to remove any information or materials, in whole or in part, in OUCET sole discretion

**OUCET** does not control or endorse the content, messages or information found in any communication service and, therefore, OUCET specifically disclaims any liability or responsibility whatsoever with regard to the communication services and any actions resulting from the user's participation in any communication service

Materials uploaded to a Communication Service may be subject to posted limitations on usage, reproduction and/or dissemination. User is responsible for keeping himself updated of and adhering to such limitations if they download the materials

**9\. TERMINATION/ACCESS RESTRICTION**

OUCET reserves the right, in its sole discretion, to terminate the access to the website and the related services or any portion thereof at any time, without notice.

**10\. QUESTIONS?**

Questions regarding this statement should be directed to the following address: [ info@ouadmissions.com](mailto:info@ouadmissions.com).
